# **NUNO JERÓNIMO**



I am a 24-year-old student pursuing a Master's degree in Engineering and Management of Information Systems. With a background in basketball, including playing for Sporting Clube de Braga and coaching the under-12 team, I have developed strong teamwork skills. I also have experience volunteering at the municipal library and contributing to my family's business. I have excellent communication skills, honed through project management and sports involvement. Additionally, I have acquired skills in programming, Arduino, IoT, and UML through my studies and internships. Motivated and driven, I aim to make a positive impact in professional environments.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021
Erasmus + Programme
University of Oulu, Finland

• Enhanced cross-cultural communication, fostering global mindset and adaptability

#### May 2019 - May 2020

Summer Internship – IOTECH

- Explored Arduino and Beacons at IOTECH, using triangulation for accurate device analysis in attendance tracking projects
- Utilized Arduino IDE, Android Studio, and LEGO® MINDSTORMS® Education EV3 for IoT exploration at IOTECH

### Mar 2019 - May 2019 Student of IOACADEMY - IOTECH

Gained expertise in IoT technology

## **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

## Municipal Library Lúcio Craveiro da Silva

Volunteer

Supported literacy and community engagement

#### Serafim da Silva Jerónimo & Filhos, Lda

Contributor

Supported business operations

#### 2013 - 2020

Basketball Player, Sporting Clube de Braga

Strong teamwork and collaboration

#### 2018 - 2020

Coach, Under-12 Basketball Team

- Experienced in coaching and mentoring young athletes, fostering teamwork, discipline, and leadership skills
- Ability to effectively communicate and motivate team members

## **EDUCATION**

Master in engineering and management of information Systems Set 2017 - Present University of Minho, Portugal

## **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese (Native) English (Proficiency)

## CONTACT

**+** +351 966 483 604

nuno.jeronimo@jeronimos.com.pt
in. https://www.linkedin.com/in/n unojeronimo-b21074182

#### **SKILLS**

- JAVA
- PYTHON
- SQL
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT
- NODE.JS
- EXPRESS.JS
- MONGODB
- ARDUINO
- BEACON
- TALEND
- PROGRAMMING (FRONT AND BACK END)
- ARDUINO
- IOT
- UML
- PROJECT MANAGER
- TEAMWORK
- COMMUNICATION
- BUSSINESS ACUMEN
- LEADERSHIP